Guide to the Bruce Davidson photographs, 1955-2008 RL.11753
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- New York: Garden Cafeteria, 1973; 6 prints
  - USA. New York City. The Cafeteria, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0156)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 73-13-36/21A-22; 52166 [150]
  - USA. New York City. Garden Cafeteria, 1973; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0157)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 73-13-37/22A; 52181 [150]
- Nudes, 1985; 4 prints
  These images seem to all derive from a photo shoot in 1985.
  - No known title, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0158)
    Other legacy identifiers: 42512 [37]
  - No known title, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 15 7/8 inches (50.80 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0159)
    Other legacy identifiers: 50274 [180]
  - No known title, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 15 7/8 inches (50.80 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0160)
    Other legacy identifiers: 50279 [180]
  - No known title, 1985; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 15 7/8 inches (50.80 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0161)
    Other legacy identifiers: 85-7-60/11; 50292 [180]. Date derived from photographer's roll number.
- Portraits, 1955-2003; 49 prints
  One of the largest series in the collection, the portraits group begins with two of Davidson's earliest images in this collection, a couple in extreme old age, taken in Patagonia, Arizona in 1955. Other portraits include well-known composers, conductors, rock musicians, politicians, authors, and artists, most based in New York City. Almost all are black-and-white prints. Titles, when present, are taken either from the print versos, or from the Magnum Photos website. A few of these portraits remain unidentified. Many of these images can be found in the photobook titled Portraits, published by Aperture in 2005.
  - The Walls, Patagonia, Arizona, 1955; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0162)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 55-3-44/29; 51116 [79]
  - John and Kate Wall, Patagonia, Arizona, 1955; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0163)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: PF 105938; 643; 51124 [79]
  - Leonard Bernstein during a rehearsal of the New York Philharmonic at Carnegie Hall, 1958; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 9 7/8 inches (20.32 x 25.08 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0164)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 58-3-61/35; 90-584/13 (Magnum); 43576 [62]. Bears stamp of Magnum Photos, London. Includes an obituary of Bernstein, who died in 1990.
  - Leonard Bernstein during a rehearsal of the New York Philharmonic at Carnegie Hall, 1958; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0165)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 58-3-53/36; 90-584/12 (Magnum); 43580 [62]. Bears stamp of Magnum Photos, London. Includes an obituary of Bernstein, who died in 1990.
  - Author Bill Styron after his publication of Lie Down in Darkness, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0166)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 59-6-2/34; 2/5; 43601 [62]. Taken in New York City.
  - Author Bill Styron after his publication of Lie Down in Darkness, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0167)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 59-6-1-58; 43606 [62]. Taken in New York City.
  - Author Bill Styron after his publication of Lie Down in Darkness, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0168)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 59-6-1/56; 43607 [62]. Taken in New York City.
  - Leonard Bernstein during a rehearsal of the NY Philharmonic at Carnegie Hall, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0169)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 59-4-52/13; 90-584/19 (Magnum); 43552 [62]. A stamp for a Finnish image service gives a Helsinki address. Includes an obituary of Bernstein, who died in 1990.
  - Samuel Beckett during the rehearsal of Waiting for Godot, 1964; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0170)
    Title source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 64-23-2/3A; 43686 [62]
  - Astronomer Dr. Harlow Shapley at home, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0171)
    Title source: print verso. Taken in Vermont. Other legacy identifiers: 65-16-1/2A; 43739 [62]
  - Carter Brown at the National Portrait Gallery, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0172)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 65-26-6-15; 47767 [107]
  - USA. Isaac Singer, author, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0173)
    Title source: other images from the same 1965 series, Magnum Photos website. Other legacy identifiers: 65-13-8-9; 43707 [62]
  - NYC, N.Y. Isaac Bashevis Singer at home., 1975; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0174)
    Title source: similar image on Magnum Photos website. Other legacy identifiers: 75-2-4-20A; 43714 [62]
  - USA. Isaac SINGER, author, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0175)
    Title source: print verso; alternate title in pencil reads "Isaac Singer at his home in NYC." Other legacy identifiers: 43720 [62]
  - NYC, N.Y. Author Isaac Singer at his Broadway home, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0176)
    Title source: print verso; alternate title in pencil reads "Isaac Singer at home on Broadway." Other legacy identifiers: 65-13-3-16A; 43722 [62]
  - At home with his wife Elodie [Robert Osborne], 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0177)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Last name on print verso spelled "Ogborn." Other legacy identifiers: 65-19-1-22; 47754 [107]
  - Robert Osborne, cartoonist, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0178)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 65-19-1-13; 47752 [107]
  - Washington, D.C. Robert Kennedy at the Senate Building, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0179)
    Title source: print verso. Alternate title in pencil reads, "New York Senator Robert Kennedy, Washington DC, Senate Building." Other legacy identifiers: 66-39-9/7-7A; 47778 [107]
  - Illinois. Senator Everett McKinley Dirksen - Republican Senator, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0180)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 66-36-14/29; 47776 [107]
  - Illinois. Senator Everett McKinley Dirksen - Republican Senator, 1966; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0181)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 66-36-14-/23; 47775 [107]
  - Mr & Mrs Edelman at home, 1969; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0182)
    Title source: print verso. Alternate title in pencil reads, "Mr. & Mrs. Marion Edelman at home." Other legacy identifiers: 69-3-2-6; 47787 [107]
  - William Styron, 1979; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0183)
    Title source: print verso. Alternate title from Magnum Photos reads, "William Styron in front of The Pink House in Coney Island." Other legacy identifiers: 79-5-4/9A-10; 47807 [107]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0184)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 84-13-2/2A; 45488 [71]. Grimsby was a journalist; in this image he is interviewing a U.S. veteran in a VA hospital or clinic setting.
  - William Styron, 1985; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0185)
    Title source: print recto label. Other legacy identifiers: 85-19; 47185 [163]
  - Author, Paul Auster, 1994; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 x 8 inches (25.40 x 20.32 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0186)
    Taken in New York City. Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 94-3-W-4/10; 47848 [107]
  - Washington, D.C. Republican Speaker of the House of Representatives Newt Gingrich, interviewed by John Perry Barlow, 1995; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 x 10 inches (20.32 x 25.40 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0187)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 47856 [107]
  - Democratic Senator Max Cleland, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0188)
    Title source: similar images from Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 99-4-11/23; 47883 [107]
  - USA. Washington, D.C. Democratic Senator Max Cleland from Georgia in his office with his staff. An explosion in the Vietnam War blew off both of his legs above the knees and one of his arms, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0189)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 99-4-15/34; 47884 [107]
  - USA. Washington, D.C. Democratic Senator Max Cleland from Georgia prays and exercises every morning before work. An explosion in the Vietnam War blew off both of his legs above the knees and one of his arms, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0190)
    Title source: Other legacy identifiers: DAB 99-4-3/22; 47885 [107]
  - USA. Washington, D.C. Democratic Senator Max Cleland from Georgia with a colleague. An explosion in the Vietnam War blew off both of his legs above the knees and one of his arms, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0191)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 99-4-8/3; 47886 [107]
  - USA. Washington, D.C. Democratic Senator Max Cleland from Georgia on his way to his office. An explosion in the Vietnam War blew off both of his legs above the knees and one of his arms, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 8 1/2 inches (27.94 x 21.59 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0192)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 99-4-10/12; 47887 [107]
  - USA. New York City. Steven Tyler looking out at a view of Manhattan, 2001; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0193)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 01-22-9/10-10A; 47899 [107]. Lead musician for Boston-based rock group Aerosmith.
  - No known title, 2001; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0194)
    Family portrait, unidentified individuals. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 01-05-6/16A; 47914 [107]
  - No known title, 2003; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0195)
    Portrait of unidentified man with woman. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2003-0-1-3/12A; 47941 [107]
  - No known title, 2003; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0196)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2003-1-3/21A; 47939 [107]
  - No known title, undated, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0197)
    According to donor inventory, this image is from the Circle Back exhibit. Other legacy identifiers: 42692 [56]
  - William Styron, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches (34.29 x 22.86 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0198)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 59-6-2/46; 72293; 40959 [14]
  - Leonard Bernstein, 1958; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 3/8 inches (34.29 x 23.81 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0199)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 58-3-21-14; 40985 [14]
  - William Styron, 1959; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches (34.29 x 22.86 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0200)
    Title source: print verso. Other legacy identifiers: 40958 [14]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0201)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 4 #33a; 48603 [116]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0202)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 4 #35a; 48602 [116]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0203)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 11 #9-9A; 48596 [116]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0204)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 11 #13-13A; 48600 [116]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0205)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 2 #22-22A; 48595 [116]
  - Roger Grimsby, 1984; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0206)
    Title source: similar image in collection (P-0184). Other legacy identifiers: DAB 84-13, 3 #5-5A; 48592 [116]
  - USA. Connecticut. Paul Newman, 2000; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 16 inches (50.80 x 40.64 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0207)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 2000-3W-5/9; 50097 [175]
  - USA. Washington, D.C. Democratic Senator Max Cleland from Georgia stretches and exercises every morning before work. An explosion in the Vietnam War blew off both of his legs above the knees and one of his arms, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 20 inches (40.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0208)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 99-4-6/30; 41700 [33]
  - No known title, undated, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 20 x 15 7/8 inches (50.80 x 40.32 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0209)
    Unidentified woman and small girl dancing outside. According to donor inventory, this image is from the Circle Back exhibit series. Other legacy identifiers: 50139 [175]
  - No known title, undated, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 16 x 19 7/8 inches (40.64 x 50.48 cm) (Box 3, Image RL.11753-P-0210)
    Close-up portrait of unidentified woman. Other legacy identifiers: 50156 [33]
- Subway, 1980; 10 prints
  These large color photographic prints feature portraits of New York City subway passengers taken by Bruce Davidson in 1980. Some of these images were published in a photobook by the same title in 1986. Print titles are taken from the Magnum Photos website.
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0211)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53216 [90]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0212)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53237 [90]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 11 x 14 inches (27.94 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0213)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53242 [90]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 24 inches (50.80 x 60.96 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0214)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53083 [86]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 24 x 20 inches (60.96 x 50.80 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0215)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53060 [86]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 23 7/8 inches (50.80 x 60.64 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0216)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 46566 [139]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Chromogenic (color) print. Dimensions: 20 x 24 inches (50.80 x 60.96 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0217)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53036 [86]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Dye transfer print. Dimensions: 20 1/8 x 23 7/8 inches (51.11 x 60.64 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0218)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53111 [87]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Dye transfer print. Dimensions: 20 x 23 7/8 inches (50.80 x 60.64 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0219)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53139 [87]
  - USA. New York City. Subway, 1980; Dye transfer print. Dimensions: 24 x 20 inches (60.96 x 50.80 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0220)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: 53147 [87]
- Time of Change: Civil Rights Photographs, 1962; 3 prints
  This series takes its name from Bruce Davidson's 2002 photobook. The three images of rural sharecroppers and urban residents were taken as Davidson documented civil rights events in Mississippi, New York City, and South Carolina. From the Magnum Photos site: "The period from 1961-1965 was the defining era of the American civil rights movement...By linking seemingly unrelated stories, Davidson shows us that there was more to the civil rights movement than the violent and racially-charged images we have so often seen. He has provided the viewer with an alternative reading of life in the North and the South, and through this promotes a reinterpretation of our understanding of equal justice and the ongoing struggle for an egalitarian future."
  - USA. New York City, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0221)
    New York City. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 62-25-395/8-8A; 52257 [151]
  - USA. Mound Bayou, Mississippi, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 13 7/8 x 11 inches (35.24 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0222)
    Mound Bayou, Mississippi. Other legacy identifiers: 52271 [151]
  - USA. South Carolina. Black Americans, 1962; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0223)
    South Carolina. Other legacy identifiers: 52363 [152]
- Other Work, 1965, 1997-1999 and undated; 6 prints
  These single prints seem to be unrelated to other series in the collection. Titles, when present, are taken from the print versos or from the Magnum Photos website.
  - No known title, after 1964; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 10 7/8 x 14 inches (27.62 x 35.56 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0224)
    From the Outside Inside exhibit series. An image taken of the demolition site of the "Underground Home" at the 1964 World's Fair, New York, soon after the Fair. Other legacy identifiers: 48621 [116]
  - No known title, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 11 x 13 7/8 inches (27.94 x 35.24 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0225)
    Other legacy identifiers: DAB 65-8-136/20; 54445 [106]
  - USA. New Jersey. The New Jersey Meadows, 1965; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 23 7/8 x 20 inches (60.64 x 50.80 cm) (Box 4, Image RL.11753-P-0226)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 65-8-48/8; 51345 [83]
  - Martha's Vineyard, 1997; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 10 7/8 inches (21.59 x 27.62 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0227)
    Title source: donor inventory. Other legacy identifiers: DAB 97-17-37/11-12; 44478 [66]
  - USA. Massachusetts, 1999; Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 8 1/2 x 11 inches (21.59 x 27.94 cm) (Box 1, Image RL.11753-P-0228)
    Title source: Magnum Photos. From the site's caption: "On December 3rd, 1999 the fire in Worcester [Massachusetts] started with a candle in an abandoned warehouse. It ended with temperatures above 3000 degrees and the men of the Worcester fire department in a fight for their lives. The fire killed 6 men. The family of Jerry Lucey. From left: John, Jeremiah III, and Michelle. When Lucey was a rookie, he called the captain of a rescue truck and told him he'd heard the squad was looking for a new man. The captain had never heard of a rookie doing such a thing, but he took him on anyway. He admired Lucey's guts. 'You can teach any man to be a good fighter,' the captain said, 'but you can't teach a good attitude.'" Other legacy identifiers: DAB 00-4-63/7; 44434 [66]
  - No known title, undated, Gelatin silver print. Dimensions: 14 x 11 inches (35.56 x 27.94 cm) (Box 2, Image RL.11753-P-0229)
    According to the donor inventory, this image is from the Circle Back exhibit series. The image is of a home interior. Other legacy identifiers: 48619 [116]